{
  "source": "HungryRaccoonStudios/SampleCards",
  "title": "English-Mandarin Letter/Sound Correlation",
  "description": "Practice your English-Mandarin letter and sound correlation",
  "translations": [
    {
      "question": "你好 -- Nǐhǎo",
      "answer": "Hello"
    },
    {
      "question": "谢谢 -- Xièxiè",
      "answer": "Thank you"
    },
    {
      "question": "对不起 -- Duìbùqǐ",
      "answer": "Sorry"
    },
    {
      "question": "不要 -- Bùyào",
      "answer": "Don't"
    },
    {
      "question": "请 -- Qǐng",
      "answer": "Please"
    },
    {
      "question": "有 -- Yǒu",
      "answer": "Have"
    },
    {
      "question": "没有 -- Méiyǒu",
      "answer": "Don't have"
    },
    {
      "question": "禁止 -- Jìnzhǐ",
      "answer": "Forbidden"
    },
    {
      "question": "出口 -- Chūkǒu",
      "answer": "Exit"
    },
    {
      "question": "入口 -- Rùkǒu",
      "answer": "Entrance"
    },
    {
      "question": "停车 -- Tíngchē",
      "answer": "Parking"
    },
    {
      "question": "医院 -- Yīyuàn",
      "answer": "Hospital"
    },
    {
      "question": "学校 -- Xuéxiào",
      "answer": "School"
    },
    {
      "question": "餐厅 -- Cāntīng",
      "answer": "Restaurant"
    },
    {
      "question": "商店 -- Shāngdiàn",
      "answer": "Store/Shop"
    },
    {
      "question": "电梯 -- Diàntī",
      "answer": "Elevator"
    },
    {
      "question": "卫生间 -- Wèishēngjiān",
      "answer": "Bathroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "紧急出口 -- Jǐnjí chūkǒu",
      "answer": "Emergency Exit"
    },
    {
      "question": "公交车站 -- Gōngjiāochē zhàn",
      "answer": "Bus Stop"
    },
    {
      "question": "地铁站 -- Dìtiě zhàn",
      "answer": "Subway Station"
    }
  ]
}
